// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not OOPS concept in Java?",
    answer: "Compilation",
    options: [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Compilation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is a type of polymorphism in Java?",
    answer: "Compile time polymorphism",
    options: [
      "Compile time polymorphism",
      "Execution time polymorphism",
      "Multiple polymorphism",
      "Multilevel polymorphism"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "When does method overloading is determined?",
    answer: "At compile time",
    options: [
      "At run time",
      "At compile time",
      "At coding time",
      "At execution time"
      ]
      
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When Overloading does not occur?",
    answer: "More than one method with same name, same number of parameters and type but different signature",
    options: [
      "More than one method with same name but different method signature and different number or type of parameters",
      "More than one method with same name, same signature but different number of signature",
      "More than one method with same name, same signature, same number of parameters but different type",
      "More than one method with same name, same number of parameters and type but different signature"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which concept of Java is a way of converting real world objects in terms of class?",
    answer: "Abstraction",
    options: [
      "Polymorphism",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Abstraction",
      "Inheritance"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Which concept of Java is achieved by combining methods and attribute into a class?",
     answer: "Encapsulation",
     options: [
       "Encapsulation",
       "Inheritance",
       "Polymorphism",
       "Abstraction"
     ]
   },
    {
     numb: 7,
     question: "What is it called if an object has its own lifecycle and there is no owner? ",
     answer: "Association",
     options: [
       "Aggregation",
       "Composition",
       "Encapsulation",
       "Association"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "What is it called where child object gets killed if parent object is killed?",
     answer: "Composition",
     options: [
       "Aggregation",
       "Composition",
       "Encapsulation",
       "Association"
     ]
   },
  {
     numb: 9,
     question: "What is it called where object has its own lifecycle and child object cannot belong to another parent object?",
     answer: "Aggregation",
     options: [
       "Aggregation",
       "Composition",
       "Encapsulation",
       "Association"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Method overriding is combination of inheritance and polymorphism?",
     answer: "True",
     options: [
       "True",
       "false",
       "Neither True nor False",
       "Incorrect Question"
     ]
   },
];